{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933143921","data":{"timestamp":" 946933143921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933148165","data":{"timestamp":" 946933148165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" START_NAYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933151598","data":{"timestamp":" 946933151598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933153150","data":{"timestamp":" 946933153149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASI"," userResponse":" NASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933156413","data":{"timestamp":" 946933156413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASI"," userResponse":" NASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933157974","data":{"timestamp":" 946933157974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933160574","data":{"timestamp":" 946933160574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933162138","data":{"timestamp":" 946933162137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZO"," userResponse":" NAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933164436","data":{"timestamp":" 946933164436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZO"," userResponse":" NAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933165996","data":{"timestamp":" 946933165996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nalo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NALO"," userResponse":" NALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933171299","data":{"timestamp":" 946933171299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nalo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NALO"," userResponse":" NALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933172863","data":{"timestamp":" 946933172863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933175300","data":{"timestamp":" 946933175300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933176859","data":{"timestamp":" 946933176859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933179982","data":{"timestamp":" 946933179982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933181529","data":{"timestamp":" 946933181529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933184232","data":{"timestamp":" 946933184232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933185780","data":{"timestamp":" 946933185779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933191136","data":{"timestamp":" 946933191136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933192718","data":{"timestamp":" 946933192717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933198548","data":{"timestamp":" 946933198548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" START_NANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933200036","data":{"timestamp":" 946933200036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933202068","data":{"timestamp":" 946933202067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933202158","data":{"timestamp":" 946933202158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.na.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933214913","data":{"timestamp":" 946933214912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235847"," gameId":" c4e7215f-d490-45db-bc4a-411b4da8666a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}